Catherwood, Martin P., Additional Papers /4052
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Martin P. Catherwood Additional Papers
1948-1979
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Catherwood, Martin P.
/4052
2 cubic feet
2 linear ft.
Papers (documents).
This collection includes many certificates, personal correspondence, many photographs. Covers the period 1902 to his death (1978)
3085047
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183 kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
R. Miles, January 13, 2016
EAD encoding:
Kheel Staff, February 22, 2019
Scope and Contents
This collection includes many certificates, personal correspondence, many photographs. Covers the period 1902 to his death (1978)
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Related Materials
Related Collections: /3025: Martin P. Catherwood Papers /4041: Martin P. Catherwood Additional Papers
Catherwood, M. P. (Martin Paul), 1904-1978; New York State School of Industrial and Labor Relations --Faculty.
3085047
- NYS Division of Commerce - Photographs, 1944 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Original - 185 pages - China Letters, 1912 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- 185 Pages - China Letters, 1900-1912 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Stones - Bills and Kenya, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- M.P. Catherwood - Personal - Miscellaneous(ILR Days - Undergrad. Days, etc.), 1948 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Board of Trustees and Executive Officers, 1947 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  Scope and Contents
  2 Photographs
- Catherwood, 1948-1954 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Congratulatory Letters - Dec. 1958-Jan. '59 rel Ind. Commissioner - Catherwood, 1958-1959 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Catherwood, 1961 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  Bound
- Congratulatory Letters - Dec. 1958-Jan.'59 - Catherwood, 1958-1959 (Box 1, Folder 10)
- Miscellaneous - Commerce Dept. Days, 1947 (Box 1, Folder 11)
- 'New York Means Business' - Catherwood (Box 1, Folder 12)
- Catherwood Friend of the NYS College of Agriculture, Founder's Roll, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 13)
- The Purdue Agricultural Alumni Association, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 14)
- 2 Photographs (Box 1, Folder 15)
- Citation of Martin Paul Catherwood, 1961 (Box 1, Folder 16)
- Dr. Martin P. Catherwood, 1978 (Box 1, Folder 17)
- Jan 12 + Other, 1970-1971 (Box 1, Folder 18)
- Photographs - ? (Box 2, Folder 1)
- M.P. Catherwood, 1902-1912 (Box 2, Folder 2)
- MPC - Copy of China Letters, 1948-1954 (Box 2, Folder 3)
- Mrs. M.P. Catherwood, 1958 (Box 2, Folder 4)
- Complete Published Work of M.P. Catherwood, 1928 (Box 2, Folder 5)
- 2 Photographs (Box 2, Folder 6)
- Citation of Martin Paul Catherwood, 1961 (Box 2, Folder 7)
- Dr. Martin P. Catherwood, 1978 (Box 2, Folder 8)
- Jan 12 + Other, 1970-1971 (Box 2, Folder 9)
- Ives Biography, 1972 (Box 2, Folder 10)
- Catherwood, 1974 (Box 2, Folder 11)
- M.P. Catherwood, 1979 (Box 2, Folder 12)
- Picture Empire State 1968 - Happy Rockefeller? - Catherwood (Box 2, Folder 13)
- Picture - Legislative Com. Dinner at Elmira (Box 2, Folder 14)
- For - Mrs. M.P. Catherwood Photo P. Rioc and girls at Dinner (Box 2, Folder 15)
  4 Photographs
- University of Illinois, 1961 (Box 2, Folder 16)
- Cornell University - M.P. Catherwood - Mr. P. Memorial Statement, 1978-1979 (Box 2, Folder 17)
- Letters - Restaurant, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 18)
- Mrs. M.P. Catherwood Highgate Road Ithaca, N.Y., 1948-1958 (Box 2, Folder 19)
- Citation of M.P. Catherwood, 1961 (Box 2, Folder 20)
- Paul Harris Fellow, 1979 (Box 2, Folder 21)
- The Joint Legislative Committee on the Taylor Law, 1971-1972 (Box 2, Folder 22)
- Martin Catherwood, 1976-1978 (Box 2, Folder 23)
- Benjamin Potoker - Memorial Award for Brotherhood, 1967 (Box 2, Folder 24)
- NYS, 1961 (Box 2, Folder 25)